roflr.com 2012-12-15

# ROFLR | Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy,   
please feel free to contact us by email at media@lolbrain.com.  
  
At www.roflr.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This   
privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and   
collected by www.roflr.com and how it is used.  
  
Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, www.roflr.com makes use of log files. The information   
inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser,   
Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number   
of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the   
site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information   
are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.  
  
Cookies and Web Beacons  
www.roflr.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences,   
record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize   
Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor  
sends via their browser.  
  
DoubleClick DART Cookie  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.roflr.com.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their   
visit to www.roflr.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and   
content network privacy policy at the following   
URL - <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>  
  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.   
Our advertising partners include ....  
Google Adsense  

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements   
and links that appear on www.roflr.com send directly to your browsers. They   
automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies   
( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party   
ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to   
personalize the advertising content that you see.  
  
www.roflr.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by   
third-party advertisers.  
  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers   
for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how   
to opt-out of certain practices. www.roflr.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and   
we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.  
  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.   
More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be   
found at the browsers' respective websites.
